<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Random Ramblings</title>
    <description>A blog to express what can't be.
</description>
    <link>http://barber.samesies.io</link>
    <atom:link href="http://barber.samesies.io/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <pubDate>Sun, 05 May 2019 01:44:03 +0530</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 05 May 2019 01:44:03 +0530</lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Jekyll v3.8.5</generator>
    
      <item>
        <title>To the one that's afraid to fall in love again.</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;You are not afraid to love. You are just afraid of not being loved back. You are just afraid of compromising and committing again. You are afraid of getting hurt again. You are not yet ready to let go of the past, because the remnants of it still haunt you.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When you are letting your emotions out and words aren’t enough to let them out so you just want to cry. Weep. It’s okay. You’ll accept that everything has already happened so you just have to deal with it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Don’t rush love. The future “right person” will give you the right love in the right timing and place. Give yourself enough time. If you aren’t ready then it’s okay. But don’t rush. Love when you are ready, not when you are lonely. You have all the time in the world. If he or she really is the right person, he/she will surely wait for you.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Be fair to yourself and to the person you’ll love in the future. You deserve to love and to be loved. Don’t close your heart in the possibility of falling in love again. Yes, you’ve been hurt before. Yes, you’ve loved and lost. Yes, you have been left behind. But that doesn’t mean that your future significant other will hurt you too. Learn to trust again. Learn to love again. Learn to commit again. Love is a big gamble: if you want to win, you have to take the risk.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To the one who’s afraid to fall in love again, don’t be. Your future partner will help you soar again. And if you happen to fall out again, somebody else will lend a hand to you. Just don’t lose faith in love.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sat, 04 May 2019 00:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
        <link>http://barber.samesies.io/2019/05/04/roof-party/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://barber.samesies.io/2019/05/04/roof-party/</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
